question_data = [
    {"category": "Animals",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Axolotl is an amphibian that can spend its whole life in a larval state.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vatican City is a country.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ottawa is the capital of Canada.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The full English name of the car manufacturer BMW is Bavarian Motor Works",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are aliens.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Need for Speed: Porsche Unleashed&quot;, the player can only drive cars"
                 " manufactured by Porsche.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A plant that has a life cycle for more than a year is known as an annual.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Books",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Shub-Niggurath is a creature that was created by \tJ. R. R. Tolkien in his novel"
                    " &quot;The Lord of The Rings&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
